Ren, I like you.
I'm sorry. I already have a girlfriend.
Is this your girlfriend?
Ren only looks blunt and cold. He's really kind at heart.
Will you continue to be my friend regardless?
Acting like nothing's happened between you and Ninako?
No one calls that "being kind".
Doesn't it bother you that I keep crushing on Ninako?
You're not being fair to me right now.
When you have a crush like mine, you'll get it.
Sorry, I won't do that ever again.
Don't hide from me.
I think he's gone now.
Thanks.
Ren?
Ando and I will handle the rest of the work here.
Why did you start avoiding me?
If I'm annoying you, just say so.
Yeah, you are.
Oh, okay.
Then you didn't need to help me out.
You could've just left me there.
Especially if we can't be friends anymore.
Did you see Ninako around?
What did you do to her?
Did you bump into her?
Was she... okay?
Answer my question first.
I kissed her.
Only on the forehead though.
Didn't I tell you she's not like those other girls of yours?
I know she's not.
That's why I caught myself, and went for her forehead instead.
I held myself back, okay?
But I do regret acting rashly.
That Ninako Kinoshita's such an idiot.
Seriously, why would she stick to a guy who rejected her?
I know right? She definitely thinks she's special.
He's just playing with her heart.
And she totally buys it!
- We won't fall for his tricks though.
- Exactly.
You should see yourselves when you're badmouthing people.
I don't care what you do, or say about me.
But could you leave Kinoshita alone?
I promise to keep my distance from her.
That's why you're avoiding me?
So those girls won't mess with me?
- What the...
- Let go.
If you want to keep pushing me around, go for it.
I won't bend so easily.
Don't let people like that ruin our friendship. That's just wrong.
Kinoshita.
You're such a weirdo.
I've discovered another reason to like him.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Really, really sorry.
I'm feeling generous today.
You're forgiven.
Thanks. Did something good happen to you?
You could say that.
Let me guess. You made up with Ren?
How could you tell?
Because I like you.
That's not something you should joke about.
Yes, ma'am.
See you around.
- Morning.
- Big news, Ninako!
Sayuri and Daiki are now officially a couple!
Really?
- Congratulations!
- Congrats, you two!
How did that go down, Daiki?
This is fatally rough.
[28/100 points]
[Episode 3]
Kinoshita?
Ren.
You're studying? But midterms just ended.
I have to retake my math exam. I scored pretty badly.
Seriously? Same here.
I'm having Ren tutor me a bit. How about you join us?
Can I?
Sure, I don't mind.
- Thanks again, dude.
- Anytime.
Manabu Miyoshi of Year 1, Class 7.
Come to the committee office.
Shoot, I forgot about that. You two get started without me.
What happens if I fail again, even after all your help?
You won't. Not on my watch.
Are you having trouble solving that equation?
See how you have the three points of the triangle
from the previous question?
Now you use the Law of cosines
to figure out the "x"
in "x-squared plus x minus 12 equals 0".
Once you've solved that, then...
Wait, you've already solved the question.
Ren, do you like math?
I love it.
I wish I could say the same thing.
Oops, I forgot we were in the library.
You're fine. We're the only ones here right now.
You're like a god.
The sun's shining down on you, to sort of give you a halo.
You've seen a god before?
Sure have. The god of math is sitting in front of me right now.
What the heck?
This is when I'd wish time would slow down a bit.
And that's all I'd wish for.
Ta-da!
We both managed to score high!
We owe it all to your tutoring. Thank you, Ren.
I only helped. Your hard work is what really paid off.
Finally, no more study sessions.
That was a long week.
On that note, I've got a favor to ask you two.
Welcome. A seat for two?
[Kyoichi MIyoshi]
- My cousin's opening a cafe soon,
- Right this way.
and is looking for part-timers to help with the grand opening.
Welcome!
Working part-time at a cafe? Sounds fun!
I wouldn't mind helping out either.
Really? Thanks, you two!
I managed to recruit Takumi as well.
Coming right up.
What?
You okay? Take it slow, and no need to panic.
Yes, thank you.
I have empty cups!
You both were amazing today.
The owner only had praises for you two.
He said your servicing skills were impeccable.
It was no biggie. I'm a jack-of-all-trades, after all.
Says the guy who got in trouble for taking a longer break.
But I was told to smile more, too.
We all have a ways to go.
I'm headed this way.
On your way to see Mayuka?
Yeah.
See you both tomorrow.
- Yeah.
- See you.
Why not just try again? Confess, and get shot down.
Maybe that will give you the closure you need.
I like the way we are now.
I'm fine with keeping these feelings to myself.
You're just trying to convince yourself.
You really think you're okay with receiving nothing in return?
Keep that up, and you'll eventually break down.
Why would you say that?
That's not your decision to make.
How was your first day of part-time work?
It was pretty busy, but fun.
That's good to hear.
Ninako's working the same job, right?
Yeah. Manabu and Ando, too.
Why do you ask?
No real reason.
I never thought you'd take up a part-time gig though.
You weren't interested in one before.
I thought I'd save up so we can go somewhere after your exams.
I see.
Smells like winter already, doesn't it?
Really? I don't smell anything different.
Trust me, it does.
What're you doing?
Giving Director his food.
This cat always hangs out around here.
[Director]
You call this cat, "Director"?
Yup. He was promoted from "Manager" just the other day.
At first, he was only an "Employee",
but with how he's fattened up,
I have to call him "Director".
No one's climbed the career ladder as fast as him.
So he's a real career cat, huh?
What do you call this kitty?
I call him "Yama the Salaryman".
- Then he's got a ways to go.
- I've never seen Ren act like that before.
Do you think Ren likes...
You can't assume anything, especially about stuff like that.
Besides, Ren has a girlfriend he cares about.
Don't stir the pot, and make his life more confusing.
Yeah, I won't.
Here's your lunch.
Thanks a million.
What's for lunch today?
Time to dig in.
Same here.
That's delicious!
I'm glad to hear it.
- Sayuri.
- Yeah?
I always appreciate you bringing lunch for me,
but doesn't it get tiring?
Not at all.
Besides, I want you to eat more than just bread every day.
I love you, Sayuri.
That came out of nowhere.
I just realized I never properly told you.
Now that I think about it,
maybe I will start bringing lunches again.
Why is that?
My dad said there's someone he wanted us to meet.
Probably the woman he wants to be his new wife.
How does that make you feel?
If my dad wants to get married again, I'll support him.
The issue is my sister.
I think she still believes the family
can be brought back together again.
So when I consider her feelings, I can't help but hesitate a bit.
[Nail Color, new polish out now!]
Want some chocolate?
Take your pick.
Then I'll take this one.
What?
There's something nice about a guy eating sweet things.
Like going to a cafe, and splitting cakes with my boyfriend?
That's a date I dream of!
I imagine I'd end up scarfing down a lot more,
and although my boyfriend would chide me,
he'd still split his share.
You look like you're having fun.
Do you do that sort of thing with Mayuka?
Mayuka doesn't eat sweet things often because of her job.
So no, I suppose not.
I see.
I try not to eat sweet things around Mayuka anyway.
[Nail Color, new polish out now!]
I'm sorry I spoke out of line the other day.
This is just a small peace offering.
It's good.
Thanks.
Is Ren your first crush?
What was your first crush like?
- Mine?
- Yeah.
My first crush was...
a girl I dated in my second year of middle school.
Really? What was she like?
She was sly girl.
She only went out with me
to get close to this other guy she liked more.
We were close friends, that guy and I.
Don't look so upset.
I'm ultimately the one who's more at fault here.
As soon as I learned I was being used,
I just left her. I didn't even try to win her over.
I'm an awful guy, who never took girls seriously since.
That's why I've decided to change.
I want to really put in effort this time.
You have a crush?
I'm currently experiencing my second real exposure to love.
Wow, I had no idea.
Good luck.
You'll root for me?
Of course.
That's the most heartening thing I could hear right now.
We'll be heading out.
- Have a good one.
- See you.
Huh? You're already done for the day?
- Mayuka?
- Hello there.
Hello.
I guess I was a tad too late.
And here I thought I'd enjoy some tea while watching Ren work.
Why not drop in anyway? I hear our cakes are pretty good.
It's fine.
I'm on a diet right now, and Ren doesn't eat sweet things anyway.
I suppose we'll see ourselves out now.
You're not bothering us. Let's go somewhere, with the four of us.
Come on, let's go.
Half-and-half.
Smells like half autumn, half winter now.
What?
I was just thinking the same thing.
Ren, I just remembered there's something I wanted to talk about.
Could we get some time alone?
Sure.
Sorry guys, but could we split here?
I'm really sorry, you two.
It's totally fine.
You two lovebirds enjoy yourselves.
Come on, let's go.
Why are you getting hurt over your own words?
I thought you were fine keeping your feelings to yourself.
I get it, okay?
No, you don't.
You can't expect anything from Ren
so long as he has a girlfriend.
You don't understand the limits there are
in your relationship with him.
Keep this up, and you'll only continue to hurt.
I know, but there's nothing I can do about it.
Sometimes, you need to make an effort to move on.
Even if that means using someone else.
What?
Use me.
I'll help you forget Ren, for good.
Ninako.
I like you.
So try experiencing romance with me.
Why are you like this, Kinoshita?
I'm only nice to girls I like.
I decided I would go with my dad of my own accord.
This is good bye.
I won't leave you.
I don't know what this is.
[Epilogue]
Great work on your first day, everyone.
I can't move...
My feet hurt...
The day ended before I could get a handle on things...
I even broke a plate.
Ren, could you organize these for me?
Sure thing.
That broken plate was a real hazard, you know?
I promise I won't break any more.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I'll do my best not to drag the rest of you down.
You should learn from her, Gacchan.
[T/N: Manabu's nickname]
I'll do my best!